Hilla Muraja - Edinburgh, UK

+447802803871 | hilla.muraja@hotmail.com | www.linkedin.com/in/hilla-muraja | https://github.com/HMuraja

Summary

I have a Diploma in Full Stack Development and advanced frontend. I have a portfolio of more than five projects to demonstrate these skills. I attended four hackathons where I had to build an application with a team in five days. Additionally, I have been working in the Life Science industry for four years, which has given me excellent problem-solving skills and ultimately led me to the path of software development!

Example Projects

- A Conceptual Website for Boutique Store Tools Used: HTML, CSS
- A Randomized Quiz Game Tools Used: HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- Instruction Terminal for Cookie Manufacturing Tools Used: HTML, CSS, Python
- Online Recipe Site for Sharing Recipes Tools Used: Django, Python
- <u>Online Book Review Platform</u> Tools Used: Django REST Framework, React, Python, JavaScript

Technical Skills

Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript ES6, Python, SQL

Databases:PostgreSQL, SQLDeployment Platform:Heroku, GitHub

Frameworks: Bootstrap, React, Django, Django REST Framework, jQuery

Design Tools: Figma, Canva, Balsamiq, diagrams.net

Relevant Experience

Code Institute - Career Development (Remote, UK)

Nov 2022 - Present

- Completed a Full Stack Developer course, earning a university credit-rated <u>Certificate</u> equivalent to the Higher National Diploma (HND).
- Completed 5 projects that were reviewed and approved by the course provider.
- Attended 4 hackathons and built 4 team projects.

Roslin CT - Manufacturing Biotechnologist (Edinburgh, UK)

May 2021 - Nov 2022

- Carried out manufacturing activities while supervising and training team members, providing successful patient treatments.
- Used analytical equipment and software and trained colleagues in their use.
- Simplified form generation with Adobe DC Pro and JavaScript, reducing version control-related problems.

Roslin CT - Technical Document Writer (Edinburgh, UK)

Oct 2020 - Apr 2021

- Revamped over 40 documents to align with industry regulations and current practices, leading to successful license approval.
- · Tracked document approval in quality management software, ensuring deadlines were respected

AstraZeneca - Medical Information and Patient Safety Coordinator (Södertälje, Sweden) Apr 2018 – Dec 2019

- Transcribed patient communication data on Salesforce and Track Wise software, securing the most complete and accurate data for product investigations.
- Organized the department's SOP transfer to the company-approved database.

Education

Code Institute2022 – 2023Full Stack Developer Diploma (View Certificate)RemoteUniversity of Turku2015 – 2018Master of Science in Genetics and PhysiologyFinland, TurkuUniversity of Turku2012 – 2015Bachelor of Science in BiologyFinland, Turku